Miami's finest are now its most wanted.
Bad Boys: Ride or Die is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Adil El Arbi.
After their late former Captain is framed, Lowrey and Burnett try to
clear his name, only to end up on the run themselves.
Mike Lowrey, played by Will Smith.
Marcus Burnett, played by Martin Lawrence.
Kelly, played by Vanessa Hudgens.
Dorn, played by Alexander Ludwig.
Rita, played by Paola Nuñez.
McGrath, played by Eric Dane.
Bad Boys: Ride or Die is a 2024 American  buddy cop action
comedy film starring Will Smith and Martin Lawrence.
The fourth installment of the Bad Boys film series, and the sequel to Bad Boys for Life (2020), it was
directed by Adil El Arbi and Bilall Fallah and written by Chris Bremner and Will Beall.
In addition to the duo, Joe Pantoliano, Vanessa Hudgens, Alexander Ludwig, Paola Núñez,
and Jacob Scipio also reprise their roles from previous installments.
Tasha Smith joins the cast as Theresa Burnett replacing Theresa Randle, who played the character in the first three
films, along with new cast members that includes Eric Dane, Ioan Gruffud, Melanie Liburd, and Rhea Seehorn.
The story follows Miami detectives Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett, who are attempting to clear the
name of their late Captain Conrad Howard after he is falsely accused of conspiracy.
Following the opening weekend box-office success of Bad Boys for Life, Sony announced plans for a fourth Bad Boys installment, with Bremner returning to write the script; however, in April
2022, production for the film was reportedly halted due to the incident with Smith slapping Chris Rock at the 2022 Academy Awards ceremony and the subsequent investigation.
Eventually, it was announced that the film was in pre-production in February 2023, with principal
photography beginning on April 3, 2023, in Atlanta, Georgia and ending on March 4, 2024.
The film premiered at Coca-Cola Arena in Dubai on May 22, 2024, and was released in the United
States on June 7 by Sony Pictures Releasing under its Columbia Pictures label.
The film grossed $405 million worldwide against a production budget of
$100 million and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of miami, florida, sequel, on
the run, police detective, buddy cop.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.